Guide to the Indivisible: Stories of American Community Records, 1999-2002 RL.10139
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Interviews and related audiovisual resources, 1999-2001; 7 boxes
  - Community recordings, 1999-2000; 1
    - Dine bi iina, Inc., Navajo Nation, 1999-2000; 4
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 8, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 29 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0090)
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 9, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 30 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0091)
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 10, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 31 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0092)
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 11, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 June 17 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0093)
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 12, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 June 23 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0094)
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 13, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0095)
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 14, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0096)
    - Eau Claire Community of Shalom, Eau Claire, South Carolina, 1999-2000; 5
      Twenty-two digital audio tapes documenting the Eau Claire Community of Shalom, an interracial, cross-denominational network concerned with revitalizing Eau Claire's historic neighborhoods and communities.
      - College Place U.M.C Columbia, SC, 11/24/1998, original DAT audio-cassette, 1998 November 24 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0106)
      - Eau Claire, tape 1, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0107)
      - Eau Claire, tape 2, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0108)
      - Eau Claire, tape 3, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0109)
      - Eau Claire, tape 4, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0110)
      - Eau Claire, tape 5, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0111)
      - Eau Claire, tape 6, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0112)
      - Eau Claire, tape 7, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0113)
      - Eau Claire, tape 8, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0114)
      - Eau Claire, tape 9, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0115)
      - Eau Claire, tape 10, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0116)
      - Eau Claire, tape 11, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0117)
      - Eau Claire, tape 12, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0118)
      - Eau Claire, tape 13, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0119)
      - Eau Claire, tape 14, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0120)
      - Eau Claire, tape 15, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0121)
      - Eau Claire, tape 16, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0122)
      - Eau Claire, tape 17, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0123)
      - Eau Claire, tape 18, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0124)
      - Eau Claire, tape 19, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0125)
      - Eau Claire, tape 20, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0126)
      - Eau Claire, tape 21, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0127)
      - Eau Claire, tape 22, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0128)
    - Haitian Citizens Police Academy and Roving Patrol, and MAD DADS Street Patrol, Delray Beach, Florida, 1999-2000; 6
      - Delray, tape 1, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 03 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0069)
      - Delray, tape 2, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 04 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0070)
      - Delray, tape 3, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 June 25 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0071)
      - Delray, tape 4, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0072)
      - Delray, tape 5, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 10 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0073)
      - Delray, tape 6, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 16 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0074)
      - Delray, tape 7, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0075)
      - Delray, tape 8, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 June 08 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0076)
      - Delray, tape 9, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0077)
      - Delray, tape 10, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 June 29 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0078)
        Fourteen digital audio tapes documenting the Haitian community in Delray Beach, Florida.
      - Delray, tape 11, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 04 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0079)
      - Delray, tape 12, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0080)
      - Delray, tape 13, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0081)
      - Delray, tape 14, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0082)
    - HandMade in America, Western North Carolina, 1999-2000; 7
      Seventeen digital audio tapes documenting a revitalization project in Marshall, North Carolina.
      - Handmade Meeting 3/12/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 March 12 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0134)
      - Red Wilson, tape 3, 03/16/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 March 16 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0145)
      - Woodrow Lail/Everette Barnette 3/17/99, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 March 17 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0137)
      - Rock Cafe/ Slowly Franklin 03/17/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 March 17 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0143)
      - Everett & Pendleton 03/18/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 March 18 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0132)
      - Depot 1 03/22/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 March 22 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0130)
      - Depot 2 03/22/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 March 22 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0131)
      - Pug Shelton/ Megan Ramsey, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 15 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0144)
      - Davitus Gosnell 05/15; Depot 05/15; Pug Shelton 5/10, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 15-18 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0133)
      - Jerry Plemmons 05/17/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 17 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0141)
      - Burke Landrum 5/18/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 18 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0138)
      - Joe Penland, Jr., Adams Drugstore 5/19/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 19 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0140)
      - Handmade Meeting, Marshall, NC, tape 1, 5/20/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 20 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0135)
      - Marshall Handmade Meeting, tape 2, Becky Anderson, 5/20, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 20 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0136)
      - Joe Penland, Jr. 5/20/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 20 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0139)
      - Becky Anderson 2/ Ray Rapp, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0129)
      - Ray Rapp (cont.); Dahryl Boone, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0142)
    - Midwifery Practice and Doula Service, University Hospital and Medical Center, Stony Brook, New York, 1999-2000; 8
      Nine digital audio tapes documenting the training of doulas in Suffolk County, New York.
      - Doula Project, tape 1, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 March 02 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0097)
      - Doula Project, tape 2, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 March 02 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0098)
      - Doula Project, tape 4, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 March 06 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0100)
      - Doula Project, tape 3, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 March 08 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0099)
      - Doula Project, tape 5, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 April 14 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0101)
      - Doula Project, tape 6, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 April 14 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0102)
      - Doula Project, tape 7, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 April 15 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0103)
      - Doula Project, tape 8, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 June 10 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0104)
      - Doula Project, tape 9, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 June 12 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0105)
    - Proyecto Azteca. San Juan, Texas, 1999-2000; 9
      Twenty-seven digital audio tapes documenting the work of Proyecto Azteca in providing housing for low-income Mexican American migrant workers.
      - Reyes 05/07/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 07 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0172)
      - David Arizmendi, tape 1, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0146)
      - David Arizmendi, tape 2, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0147)
      - Amado Balderas, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0148)
      - Teresa Barera, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0149)
      - Jose Chavez, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0150)
      - Contreras, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0151)
      - Veronica Cruz, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0152)
      - Dani's Class, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0153)
      - Gaona, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0154)
      - Miguel Angel Garcia, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0155)
      - Yolanda Hernandez, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0156)
      - Group at PA, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0157)
      - Olga Valle Viera, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0158)
      - Noe Hinojosa, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0159)
      - Glynnis Laing, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0160)
      - Ricardo Longoria, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0161)
      - Patricia Mejia, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0162)
      - Elizabeth Morales, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0163)
      - Alicia Mabejas, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0164)
      - Nerio, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0165)
      - Leslie Nemmon, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0166)
      - Melissa Perez, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0167)
      - Omar Perez, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0168)
      - Arturo Ramirez, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0169)
      - The Pulga, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0170)
      - Sound, etc., original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0171)
    - Southwest Youth Collaborative, Chicago, Illinois, 1999-2000; 10
      Eight digital audio tapes documenting the efforts of Chicago youth to improve access to quality education and youth development programs.
      - SW Youth Collaborative, tape 1, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0001)
      - SW Youth Collaborative, tape 2, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0002)
      - SW Youth Collaborative, tape 3, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0003)
      - SW Youth Collaborative, tape 4, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0004)
      - SW Youth Collaborative, tape 5, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0005)
      - SW Youth Collaborative, tape 6, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0006)
      - Indivisible, tape 7, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0007)
      - Indivisible, tape 8, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0008)
    - The Village of Arts and Humanities, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1999-2000; 11
      Twelve digital audio tapes produced by the Talking Cloth project, in which nine teenagers document the creation of a community quilt.
      - Indivisible/Village, tape 1, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 March 17 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0009)
      - Indivisible/Village, tape 2, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0010)
      - Indivisible/Village, tape 3, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 April 09 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0011)
      - Indivisible/Village, tape 4, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 April 09 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0012)
      - Indivisible/Village, tape 5, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0013)
      - Indivisible/Village, tape 6, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 April 16-17 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0014)
      - Indivisible/Village, tape 7, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0015)
      - Indivisible/Village, tape 8, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0016)
      - Indivisible/Village, tape 9, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 June 18 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0017)
      - Indivisible/Village, tape 10, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 June 25 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0018)
      - Indivisible/Village, tape 11, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 July 07 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0019)
      - 5/23/01 Village of Arts and Humanities, original DAT audio-cassette, 2001 May 23 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0020)
    - Yaak Valley Forest Community, Yaak Valley, MT, 1999-2000; 13
      Thirty-six audiocassettes documenting a collaborative project of the Yaak Valley Forest Community and the Troy School District in Yaak Valley, Montana, on ecological diversity and forest protection.
      - Jeanne Higgins, Libby, MT, 06/06/99, also present Terry Evans & Eddie Randles, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 06 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0061)
      - Gale & Carolyn Bennett, Yaak, MT, 6/17/99, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 17 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0005)
      - Rick Bass, 6/18/99, Yaak, MT (Interview), original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 18 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0007)
      - Zeita Mae Romeiko, Yaak River, MT, 6/18/99 (J. Lund), original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 18 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0065)
      - Zeita Mae Romeiko, Yaak, MT, 6/18/99, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 18 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0066)
      - Yaak - Dave Henderson, 6/19/99, Troy, MT (J. Lund), original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 19 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0062)
      - Dave Henderson, Troy, MT, 6/19/99, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 19 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0063)
      - Yaak Valley Community Church Service, Yaak, MT, Sunday Morning Service, 6/20/99, 1 of 2, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 20 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0014)
      - Yaak Valley Community Church Service, Yaak, MT, Sunday Morning Service, 6/20/99, 2 of 2, very short, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 20 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0015)
      - Martin & Joanne Riedlinger, Yaak, MT, 6/20/99, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 20 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0067)
      - Martin & Joanne Riedlinger, Yaak, MT, 6/20/99 (J. Lund), original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 20 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0068)
      - Dario Scarabosio, Yaak, MT, 6/21/99, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 21 (Box 22, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0097)
      - Jesse Sedler, Horse Logging, Yaak, MT, 6/21/99, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 21 (Box 22, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0102)
      - Logging with Michael "Crash" Karuzas and Dan Kelly, Yaak, MT, 6/22/99, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 22 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0059)
      - Yaak - Larry Dolezal, Troy, MT (J. Lund), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0002)
      - Larry Dolezal, Troy, MT, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0003)
      - Scott Daily, Yaak, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0004)
      - Rick Bass in the woods, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0006)
      - Yaak Valley Forest Council, Forest Walk for Stewardship Project, Tape 1 of 3, Rick Bass, Steve Thompson, Scott Dailey, Robyn King, also Terry Evans, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0009)
      - Yaak Valley Forest Council, Forest Walk for Stewardship Project, Tape 1 of 3, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0010)
      - Yaak Valley Forest Council, Forest Walk for Stewardship (Roderick Site), Tape 2 of 3, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0011)
      - Yaak Valley Forest Council, Forest Walk for Stewardship (Roderick Site), Tape 3 of 3, very short, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0012)
      - Yaak Valley Forest Council, Forest Walk for Stewardship, Tape 3 of 3, short, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0013)
      - Jimmy Martin & Robyn King, 1, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0055)
      - Jimmy Martin & Robyn King, 2, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0056)
      - Mikolas "Crash" Karuzas & Shirley Karuzas, also Haakon & Aaron Karuzas & Tyler Janssen, 1, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0057)
      - Mikolas "Crash" Karuzas & Shirley Karuzas, 2, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0058)
      - Tom Horelick, Libby, MT, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0060)
      - John, Barbara, and Willow Lindsay, Yaak (J. Lund), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0071)
      - Tim & Joanne Candler Linehan, Yaak, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0072)
      - Reuben Knellen, Yaak, MT (sawmill & interview), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0073)
      - John, Barb, & Willow Lindsay, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0074)
      - John & Mary Ellen Solem, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 22, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0095)
      - John & Mary Ellen Solem, Yaak (J. Lund), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 22, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0096)
      - James "Seamus" Sedler & Jesse Sedler, Yaak, MT (Lund), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 22, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0099)
      - James "Seamus" Sedler & Jesse Sedler, Yaak, MT, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 22, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0103)
    - Unidentified -- associated interviews, 1999-2000; 12
      - Mark & Simone Ewing, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0001)
      - Jeanette Aklin & Artie Wright, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0008)
      - Keith & Susanne Hagerty, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0064)
      - Tom & Nancy Oar (1), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0069)
      - Tom & Nancy Oar (2), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0070)
      - Ted Schmidt & Patti O'Bryan, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 22, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0098)
      - Linda Stehlik (1), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 22, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0100)
      - Linda Stehlik (2), Side A only, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 22, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0101)
  - Associated Media, 1999-2000; 2
    - Indivisible Exhibit, KVOA, 9/06/1999, original VHS video-cassette, 1999 September 6 (Box 26, Video-cassette RL10139-VHS-0001)
    - Indivisible Chicago VNR, with R. Suarez and Ali, B-Roll and photographs, 9/20/00, original VHS video-cassette, 2000 September 20 (Box 26, Video-cassette RL10139-VHS-0002)
    - Indivisible PSA 9/20/2000, original VHS video-cassette, 2000 September 20 (Box 26, Video-cassette RL10139-VHS-0003)
    - Invisible on NPR's Morning Edition, Bob Edwards and Tom Rankin, January 8, 2001, original standard audio-cassette, 2001 January 08 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0045)
    - Exhibit 12/14/2001, UNC TV, original VHS video-cassette, 2001 December 14 (Box 26, Video-cassette RL10139-VHS-0004)
- Photographs, 1999-2002; 4; 20 boxes
  Prints in various sizes, chiefly in black and white, taken by documentary photographers in project locations: Alaska, Arizona, California, Florida, Illinois, Montana, New Mexico, New York, and Wisconsin. All captions and contextual notes have been taken from the original source. Unless otherwise noted, images were also published in the volume, Indivisible: Stories of American Community, and formed the traveling exhibit by the same name. Each print is prefaced by a unique identification number assigned by the photographers. Arranged in subseries alphabetically by photographer's last name.
  - Dawoud Bey (United States, b. 1953), 1
    Seventeen black and white gelatin silver prints of community organizations and individuals in Chicago, Illinois, with the chief focus on members of the Southwest Youth Collaborative, an effort on the part of faith-based institutions, social service centers, recreational centers, and neighborhood organizations to empower youth and their community in South Chicago neighborhoods.
    - Danyale, West Englewood Youth and Teen Center, 1999 (2 prints) (Box 37, Item (L2000:040:001a-b))
      Scope and Contents note
      (2 prints)
    - Aron Hanson, Youth Organizer, Community Justice Initiative, 1999 (5 prints) (Box 37, Item (L2000:040:002a-b, L2000:040:003, L2000:040:004, L2000:040:005))
      (5 prints)
    - Trenton, Greater Lawn Community Youth Network, 1999 (Box 37, Item (L2000:040:006))
    - Adriana Bartow, Director, Greater Lawn Community Youth Network, 1999 (Box 37, Item (L2000:040:007))
    - Darrin, West Englewood Youth and Teen Center, 1999 (Box 37, Item (L2000:040:008))